Register to the Vladimir Konkordovich Abdank-Kossovskii Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1916-1961.
  - Kolchak, Admiral Aleksandr Vasil'evich, 1919. (Folder 54: 5)
    One print
  - Nicholas II and family. Fifty prints (Folder 54: 6)
  - Pilevskii, Nikolai Nikiforovich, and various unidentified individuals, 1921-1961 and undated. (Folder 54: 7)
    Twelve prints, three negatives
  - Russian officers in emigration, 1916-1953. (Folder 54: 8)
    Nineteen prints
  - Russian Orthodox Church, 1927-1959 and undated. (Folder 54: 9)
    Sixty prints
  - "Zarubezhnaia Rus'" exhibit, undated. (Folder 54: 10)
    Eight negatives
- Oversize File, 1936. (Box 55)
  Zhiganov, Vladimir Daniilovich, Russkie v Shangkhaie, 1936. Printed copy
- Printed Matter, undated. (Box 56-60)
  Clippings from various émigré newspapers and other sources. Box 57-60 not filmed. Originals retained by Holy Trinity Orthodox Seminary